Guide to the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Fishermen and Allied Workers Division, Local 3 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- INTERNATIONAL LONGSHOREMEN'S AND WAREHOUSEMEN'S UNION. INTERNATIONAL. FISHERMEN AND ALLIED WORKERS DIVISION. LOCAL #3., 1938-1982; RECORDS SUBGROUP 7 (Box-folder 13/1-17/17)
  - WORKING AGREEMENTS, 1938-1980; SERIES VI (Box-folder 14/34-14/54, 15/1-15/45)
    - Puget Sound Fish Cannery Workers Agreement- Tidewater Packing Company, Inc., 1952 (Box-folder 15/26)
    - Herring Agreement, Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Agreement, Supplemental Agreement, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 15/27)
    - Herring Agreement Signed by Storford and Grondahl Packing Co. and Buchan and Heinen Packing Co. with Supplemental Agreements, 1953 (Box-folder 15/28)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreements- Port Moller and False Pass Owner Signed Agreements, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 15/29)
    - Boat Income/Expense Records, 1953 (Box-folder 15/30)
    - Signed Supplemental Agreements-Lars Anderson Fish Co. and Dungeness Crab Co., 1952 (Box-folder 15/31)
    - Salmon Price. Memoranda of Understanding on Weighing. Puget Sound Salmon Draft, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 15/32)
    - Purse Seine Agreement, Marine Engineers Beneficial Association Agreement, Southeast Alaska Salmon Agreement, Puget Sound Crab Processors Agreement, Independent Fishmen Agreement, Company Fishermen Agreement, Southwestern Seine Agreement., 1953 (Box-folder 15/33)
    - Herring Shoreworkers Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Agreement (Storfold and Grohndahl, Buchan and Heinen, Thumb Bay Packers), Lease, 1954 (Box-folder 15/34)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreements- Port Moller and False Pass Owner Signed Agreements, 1954 (Box-folder 15/35)
    - Puget Sound Fish Cannery Workers Agreement, 1954 (Box-folder 15/36)
    - Tendermen's Agreements, 1954 (Box-folder 15/37)
    - Amalgamated Meatcutter and Butcher Workers of America, Tacoma Plant American Smelting and Refining Co., Prince William Sound, and Salmon Agreements, Southeastern Alaska Seine Boat Owners Suggested Regulations, 1954 (Box-folder 15/38)
    - Herring Agreements- Storfold and Grohndahl Packing Co. and Buchan and Heinen Packing Co., 1955 (Box-folder 15/39)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Agreement- Fishermen's Packing Corp., Anacortes Cannery, 1955 (Box-folder 15/40)
    - Puget Sound Fish Cannery Workers. Puget Sound Crab Processors., 1955 (Box-folder 15/41)
    - Tendermen's Agreements, 1955 (Box-folder 15/42)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Supplemental Agreement- Fall Season, 1955 (Box-folder 15/43)
    - Kodiak and Westward Salmon Agreement, Watchmen Agreement, Networkers Supplement, Women Cannery Workers Agreement, Cannery Machinemen and Misc. Male Classifications, Master Agreement, Fresh Fish and Cold Storage, Reduction Plant Supplementary Agreement, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 15/44)
    - Deep Sea Agreements- King Crab, 1956 (Box-folder 15/45)
  - PRICE NEGOTIATIONS, 1950-1959; SERIES VII (Box-folder 15/46-15/51, 16/3, 16/10)
    - Fall Price Negotiations and Meetings, 1950 (Box-folder 15/46)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1951 (Box-folder 15/47)
    - Puget Sound Fall Negotiations, 1953 (Box-folder 15/48)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Negotiations, 1955 (Box-folder 15/49)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Negotiations-Ballots, 1955 (Box-folder 15/50)
    - Herring Plant Negotiations, 1959 (Box-folder 15/51)
    - Purse Seine Negotiations, 1956 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Herring Plant Negotiations- Storfold and Grondahl, 1956 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - PRICE AGREEMENTS, 1951-1962; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 16/1-16/2, 16/4-16/5, 16/7-16/9)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreement, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - False Pass and Port Moller Agreements, 1956 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Fishing Gear. Salmon. Salmon Seine. Alaska Salmon Industry Inc.. Fall Chum. Herring. Sacramento River. BSFU General., 1952 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Agreements, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreements, 1955 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Herring Settlement- Southeast Alaska, 1951 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Herring Settlement- Prince William Sound, 1951 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1950-1981; SERIES IX (Box-folder 16/6, 16/11-16/21)
    - Vessel Financial Record Sheets, 1954 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Storfold and Grondahl Packing Co. Financial Records, 1962 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - General Ledger, 1951 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Balance Per Bank Statement (Outstanding Checks). Records Submitted to National Labor Relations Board. Balance Sheets. Statements of Cash Receipts and Disbursements. Resolutions., 1950-1951 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Leger Sheets, Bank Deposit Receipts, 1951 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Taxes, 1951 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Employee Records, 1951 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Assorted Receipts and Expenses, 1979 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Financial Statements, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Financial Statements and Secretary Treasurer's Reports, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Secretary Treasurer's Reports, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Secretary Treasurer's Reports, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - REPORTS, 1949-1978; SERIES X (Box-folder 16/22-16/24, 17/15)
    - "Report from Europe by the Rank and File Delegation of the ILWU", 1949 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - "The Fisheries of California: The Industry, The Men, Their Union", 1947 (Box-folder 16/23)
    - Delegates Report- United Arab Republic (Egypt), circa 1966 (Box-folder 16/24)
    - Puget Sound Commercial Salmon Management and Catch Reporting Areas, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - ILWU TRAILS AND CLAIMS, 1936, 1941-1959; SERIES XI (Box-folder 19/9-19/17)
    - Charges, 1949 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Claims Settled, 1949 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Claims Settled, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - International Trails, 1936, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Washington Unemployment Compensation Tax, 1950 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - United States of America v. Henry Renton Bridges, 1950 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Charges, 1949-1955 (bulk 1955) (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Puget Sound Canneries, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Tadich and Bettelli v. Cummings, 1955 (Box-folder 19/17)
  - NEWSLETTERS AND REPORTS, 1957-1980; SERIES XII (Box-folder 16/25-16/26, 17/1-17/9)
    - The Purse Line Newsletter, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Assorted Newsletters: Alaskero News, Emergency Feeding Program's Feedback, American Income Life Labor Letter, The Hook, SEIU 6, Warehouse News, ILWU Washington Report, Oil Ports Inquiry News, American Labor, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 16/26)
    - Memorandums- State of Alaska, Office of the Governor- International Fisheries and External Affairs, 1978 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Pacific Marine Fisheries Commission Newsletters, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Columbia Basin Salmon and Steelhead Report, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - International Pacific Salmon Fisheries Commission News Releases, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Catch and Production Commercial Fisheries Statistics- Alaska, 1975, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Labor Agency of King County Labor Council, AFL-CIO- Community Services Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Washington State Department of Fisheries - News Release, 1980 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Washington State Department of Fisheries - News Release, 1979 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Washington State Department of Fisheries - News Release, 1978 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - WASHINGTON STATE LEGISLATURE - MEETING SCHEDULES. RELEASES. NOTICES OF MEETINGS., 1978-1980; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 17/10)
  - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1948-1981; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 17/11-17/13)
    - First Conference of Alaska FTA Locals, 1948 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Proceedings of the 10th Constitutional Convention of the CIO, Report of Resolutions Committee, 1948 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - ILWU 24th Biennial Convention Minutes and Resolutions, May 1981 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - EPHEMERA, 1945-circa 1980; SERIES XV (Box-folder 17/14, 17/16-17/17)
    - Handwritten Office Notes and Lists (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Assorted Picket Signs. Union Brochures. ILWU Constitutions. Benefits Pamphlets. Organizing Pamphlets., 1959-1965 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - "The Truth About Unions" by Leo Huberman. "Joe Worker and the Story of Labor" Comic Book., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD NOTES AND MINUTES, 1955; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 17/18)
  - FISHERMEN AND SHOREWORKERS TRUST FUND, 1952-1975; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 17/19-17/27)
    - Dissolution of Fishermen and Shoreworkers Trust Fund, 1969, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Trustee Meeting Minutes, 1952, 1956-1971 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Declaration of Trust and Welfare Plan, 1952, 1955, 1961 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Northwestern Insurance Policy, 1952-1953, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Reports on Examination of Financial Statements, 1959-1971 (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Agreement and Declaration of Fishermen and Shoreworkers Trust, 1952, 1972 (Box-folder 17/24)
    - Insurance Commissioner Reports and Correspondence, 1955-1958, 1966 (Box-folder 17/25)
    - Fidelity bonds, 1952-1953, 1956, 1958-1961, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Government and Legal Papers, 1957-1960, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 17/27)
- EXTERNAL ORGANIZATION: WASHINGTON STATE INDUSTRIAL UNION COUNCIL, 1940-1949; RECORDS SUBGROUP 8 (Box-folder 18/1-18/6, 18/13)
  - Reports, Resolutions, Minutes, 1945 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Convention Proceedings, Minutes, "To All Seamen and Port Workers" Flier, 1944 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Washington State Industrial Union Council CIO Fifth Annual Convention Proceedings, 1943 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Reports and Minutes, 1943, 1949 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - CIO Constitution Constitution of the Washington State Industrial Union Council. Washington State CIO Convention. CIO Executive Board., 1948 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Legislative and Political Action Conference, 1946 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Statement of Fact and Analysis Regarding Washington State Industrial Council Convention, 1940 (Box-folder 18/13)
- EXTERNAL ORGANIZATION: MARITIME FEDERATION OF THE PACIFIC, 1937-1971; RECORDS SUBGROUP 9 (Box-folder 18/7-18/12, 18/14-18/18)
  - State Examiner's Report of the Fishermen and Shoreworker's Trust Fund, 1957-1958, 1965 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Fishermen and Shoreworker's Fund General Correspondence, 1959, 1962-1964, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Paul Pinksy of Union Insurance Consultants, Inc. Correspondence Re: Fishermen and Shoreworker's Fund, 1958-1961, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Certificate of Authority for Fishermen and Shoreworker's Trust Fund. Employee Welfare Trust Fund Documentation, 1952, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Buchan Packing Company Summons. Storfold and Grondahl Packing Company Suit, 1957-1958, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Federal and State Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Acts, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Minutes of the Washington District 1 Council of the Maritime Federation of the Pacific, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Minutes of the Washington District 1 Council of the Maritime Federation of the Pacific, 1939 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Trial of Nick Petrinovich, Pacific Coast Fisherman's Union Injunction Appeal, Union Agreement Provisions, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Alaska Conventions (FRAGILE), 1937 (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Alaska Conventions, 1938, 1941 (Box-folder 18/18)
- EXTERNAL ORGANIZATION: SEATTLE CIO COUNCIL, 1944-1949; RECORDS SUBGROUP 10 (Box-folder 18/19-18/21)
  - Washington State Industrial Union Council Eleventh and Seventh Annual Conventions, 1945, 1949 (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Minutes and Calls to Action - includes Harry Bridges Deportation, Actions pertaining to World War II, Japanese Internment, 1945 (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Minutes and Calls to Action, 1944 (Box-folder 18/21)
- EXTERNAL ORGANIZATION: SALMON CONSERVATION LEAGUE - Newspaper Clippings, Financial Records, Correspondence, Water Pollution in the United States, 1944; RECORDS SUBGROUP 11 (Box-folder 18/22)
- EXTERNAL ORGANIZATION: GOVERNOR'S PINK SALMON ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1954-1956; RECORDS SUBGROUP 12 (Box-folder 18/23)
- EXTERNAL ORGANIZATION: WASHINGTON COMMONWEATLH FEDERATION MINUTES, 1944; RECORDS SUBGROUP 13 (Box-folder 18/24)